「Rubia」
Life  blooms  like  a  flower
生命如花朵绽放
far  away  or  by  the  road
或许遥远  或许就在路边
waiting  for  the  one
等待着那个人
to  find  the  way  back  home
找到回归的路
Rain  falls  a  thousand  times
雨水数千次的冲刷
No  footprints  of  come-and-go
已经分辨不清来往的脚印
You  who  once  went  by
曾经过此处的你
where  will  you  belong
终将属于哪里
I  feel  your  sigh  and  breath
我察觉到你的叹息与呼吸
In  the  last  blow  of  wind
在风最后的呼啸之中
Not  yet  for  the  story  on  the  last  page
还未到将故事翻至末页的时候
It's  not  the  end
所以一切还未结束
Life  blooms  like  a  flower
生命如花朵绽放
far  away  or  by  the  road
或许遥远  或许就在路边
waiting  for  the  one
等待着那个人
to  find  the  way  back  home
找到回归的路
Time  flows  across  the  world
时光流淌过天地间
There  is  always  a  longer  way  to  go
我的旅程不会结束
Till  I  reach  your  arms
直至能与你相拥
a  Madder  there  for  you
并献上一株茜草
Up  against  the  stream
沿着溪流向上
waterways  will  join  as  one
无数水流终将合一
Tracing  to  the  source
追溯着源头
No  more  strayed  or  lost
便可不再迷惘
You  will  see  petals  fly
你将看见花瓣纷飞
when  lament  becomes  carol
当悲伤之音转而歌颂
Could  you  please  hear  my  voice
请你听见我的声音
that  hungers  for  a  duo
正渴望与你二重唱
Life  blooms  like  a  flower
生命如花朵绽放
far  away  or  by  the  road
或许遥远  或许就在路边
waiting  for  the  one
等待着那个人
to  find  the  way  back  home
找到回归的路
Time  flows  across  the  world
时光流淌过天地间
There  is  always  a  longer  way  to  go
我的旅程不会结束
Till  I  reach  your  arms
直至能与你相拥
a  Madder  there  for  you
并献上一株茜草
Life  blooms  like  a  flower
生命如花朵绽放
far  away  or  by  the  road
或许遥远  或许就在路边
waiting  for  the  one
等待着那个人
to  find  the  way  back  home
找到回归的路
Time  flows  across  the  world
时光流淌过天地间
There  is  always  a  longer  way  to  go
我的旅程不会结束
Till  I  reach  your  arms
直至能与你相拥
a  Madder  there  for  you
并献上一株茜草
《幽灵公主》ED:「もののけ姫」
はりつめた弓の
BGM「ウィアートル」
(その胸の  中には何  があるの)
(愛になって)
(光の)
太陽は昇るから  きっと
BGM「ウィアートル」
(落ちた涙は)
(あふれそうな)
優しさを
見せてくれる
もう一度
BGM「ウィアートル」
中には何があるの
歩き出す  愛になって
光の中へ
大丈夫
どんな未来でも
太陽は昇るから
BGM「ウィアートル」
(あふれそうな)  優しさを
見せてくれる
もう一度  笑って
その胸の中には何があるの
歩き出す  愛になって
光の中へ
大丈夫  どんな未来でも
太陽は昇るから  きっと