Do you known lizard hot pot?
Lizard hot pot?
No
In Indonesia?
First, I've ... I don't think I've ever been to Indonesia
君の quadlingo
Lizard hot pot?
Lizard!
I ...
I don't ...
Lizard hot pot? Lizard
Lizard hot pot!
Wait *5, I'm going to searching it
这个是什么？
待って  待って  待って
我看到 wait wait wait
谢谢 SC 待って 待って
Lizard Oh dame
Kimo!
It looks so worse
Wait wait wait. I'm Doing searching
No ~
Oh, It looks so gross! No~
No
I'm scared. No, I'm scared *4
No, I'm so scared. OMG My eyes
ごめんなさい 我看到
I'm searching lizard hot pot
I google searched
I google searched. NO
No It ...
OMG
What the hell?
No I'm going to show you gays a picture
I'm so scared. I get immediately like ...
I'm trying to like ... lizard
Hey hey lizard, Hey lizard
No
Really?
No I ... NO
You never see that. No it's so ...
No I'm trying to look at it again
No no no. I can't *N. No no no
You gays can search it for yourself. It so ..
I can't. I'm scared of lizards
No, I'm really scared of lizards
So, Seeing that I'm like ...
Scared now. 我害怕了
I'm really scared of lizards
I'm really really scared of lizards
I'm not joking. I'm so scared of lizards
Lizard totally like ...
only thing I'm super scared of
Lizard taste like chicken. No ~
No no no
I don't need lizard. It is OK?
I don't ...
Monkey? No no no. 不可以