「夜花夜夜夜奏花」
「千弦沢」
「peanut」
「耗子永远是maguni」
「来晚了  昼ご飯美味しかった」
「ShadoW」
「木笹」
「千本桜」
大胆不敵に  ハイカラ革命
大胆无畏洋化革命
磊々落々  反戦国家
光明磊落反战国家
日の丸印の二輪車転がし
骑着日之丸印的二轮车
悪霊退散  ICBM
恶灵退散  ICBM
環状線を走り抜けて
奔驰穿过环状线
東奔西走なんのその
东奔西走不算什么
少年少女戦国無双
少年少女战国无双
浮世の随に
跟从着浮世浪
千本桜  夜ニ紛レ
千本樱溶入夜中
君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
连你的声音也传不到啊
此処は宴  鋼の檻
此处开宴钢铁牢笼中
その断頭台で見下ろして
自那断头台上往下看吧
三千世界  常世之闇
三千世界黄泉之暗
嘆ク唄モ聞コエナイヨ
连哀叹之歌也听不见啊
青藍の空  遥か彼方
青蓝天空遥远彼端
その光線銃で打ち抜いて
就用那光线枪射穿吧
百戦錬磨の見た目は将校
看来身经百战实为将校
いったりきたりの花魁道中
人潮来往的花魁道中
アイツもコイツも皆で集まれ
不管那个人或这个人大家都过来吧
聖者の行進
圣者的行进
ワン  ツー  サン  シー
一二三四
禅定門を潜り抜けて
穿过出家僧人旁
安楽浄土厄払い
安乐净土驱凶避邪
きっと終幕は大団円
最后一幕一定就是大团圆
拍手の合間に
在掌声的同时
千本桜  夜ニ紛レ
千本樱溶入夜中
君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
连你的声音也传不到啊
此処は宴  鋼の檻
此处开宴钢铁牢笼中
その断頭台で見下ろして
自那断头台上往下看吧
三千世界  常世之闇
三千世界黄泉之暗
嘆ク唄モ聞コエナイヨ
连哀叹之歌也听不见啊
希望の丘  遥か彼方
希望之丘遥远彼端
その閃光弾を打ち上げろ
就将那闪光弹射入天吧
環状線を走り抜けて
奔驰穿过环状线
東奔西走なんのその
东奔西走不算什么
少年少女戦国無双
少年少女战国无双
浮世の随に
跟从著浮世浪
千本桜  夜ニ紛レ
千本樱溶入夜中
君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
连你的声音也传不到啊
此処は宴  鋼の檻
此处开宴钢铁牢笼中
その断頭台を飛び降りて
自那断头台上跳下来吧
千本桜  夜ニ紛レ
千本樱溶入夜中
君が歌い僕は踊る
你歌我舞
此処は宴  鋼の檻
此处开宴钢铁牢笼中
さあ光線銃を撃ちまくれ
扣下光线枪的板机吧
「TheCrazyEmbErs」
「Herne」
「橘子大天使」
「软妹(何在)」
「想成为绅士的DIO」
「(我)单推Inga」
「希樱飘落」
「Bloody  stream」
「Atelier  Ryza」
「アリオスーArios」
「Ricoh」
「龙姬酱」
「王酸奶单挑(军一号)」
「」
「You  Belong  with  Me」
You're  on  the  phone  with  your  girlfriend
你正和女朋友通着电话
She's  upset
她生气了
She's  going  off  about  something  that  you  said
好像是你说错了话
Cause  she  doesn't,  get  your  humor  like  I  do
因为她不像我一样懂你的幽默之处
I'm  in  the  room,  it's  a  typical  Tuesday  night
又是一个独自宅在家的周二
I'm  listening  to  the  kind  of  music  she  doesn't  like
我正听着她不喜欢的音乐
And  she'll  never  know  your  story  like  I  do
她永远不会像我一样了解你
But  she  wears  short  skirts
她穿着短裙
I  wear  T-shirts
而我穿着T恤
She's  cheer  captain
她是啦啦队队长
And  I'm  on  the  bleachers
我却在看台上
Dreaming  about  the  day  when  you  wake  up
幻想你哪天突然清醒
And  find  that  what  you're  looking  for
发现你一直寻找的那个人
Has  been  here  the  whole  time
已经在你身边
If  you  could  see  that
如果你能察觉到
I'm  the  one  who  understands  you
我就是最了解你的人
Been  here  all  along  so  why  can't  you  see
我一直在这里  你为什么视而不见
You  belong  with  me
我们是天生一对
天生一对
Walk  in  the  streets  with  you  in  your  worn-out  jeans
你穿着破牛仔裤和我一起闲逛
I  can't  help  thinking  this  is  how  it  ought  to  be
我情不自禁地去幻想这一幕情景
Laughing  on  a  park  bench,  thinking  to  myself
一边跟你说笑  一边在想
Hey  isn't  this  easy
嘿不就是这样
And  you've  got  a  smile  that
你的微笑
Could  light  up  this  whole  town
可以照亮整个城镇
I  haven't  seen  it  in  a  while  since  she  brought  you  down
自从她伤了你的心后我就再没见过
You  say  you're  fine
你说你没事
I  know  you  better  than  that
但我太了解你
Hey  what  you  doing  with  a  girl  like  that
嘿面对那样的女孩你会怎样
She  wears  high  heels
她穿着高跟鞋
I  wear  sneakers
我穿着运动鞋
Shes  cheer  captain  and
她是啦啦队队长
I'm  on  the  bleachers
我却在看台上
Dreaming  about  the  day  when  you  wake  up
幻想你哪天突然清醒
And  find  that  what  you're  looking  for
发现你一直寻找的那个人
Has  been  here  the  whole  time
已经在你身边
If  you  could  see  that  I'm  the  one  who  understands  you
如果你能察觉到我就是最了解你的人
Been  here  all  along  so  why  can't  you  see
我一直在这里  你为什么视而不见
You  belong  with  me
我们是天生一对
Standing  by  and  waiting  at  your  back  door
站在你家后门等你
all  this  time  how  could  you  not  know  Baby
亲爱的你为何一直没能察觉
You  belong  with  me
我们是天生一对
天生一对
Oh  I  remember
我记得
You  driving  to  my  house  in  the  middle  of  the  night
你半夜开车去我家
I'm  the  one  who  makes  you  laugh
当你非常难过的时候
When  you  know  you're  about  to  cry
我是唯一能逗笑你的人
I  know  your  favorite  songs
我知道你最喜欢的歌
And  you  tell  me  about  your  dreams
你也告诉我你的理想
I  think  I  know  where  you  belong
我知道你的归宿
I  think  I  know  it's  with  me
你应该和我在一起
Can't  you  see  that  I'm  the  one  who  understands  you
你难道看不出来我是懂你的人
Been  here  all  along
我一直在这里
So  why  can't  you  see
你为什么视而不见
You  belong  with  me
我们是天生一对
Standing  by  waiting  at  your  back  door
我站在门后偷偷等你
All  this  time,  How  could  you  not  know  Baby
亲爱的你为何一直没能察觉
You  belong  with  me
我们在一起才合适
我们是天生一对
You  belong  with  me
天生一对
Have  you  ever  thought  just  maybe
你有没有想过这种可能呢
You  belong  with  me
我们是天生一对
天生一对
「我最后的波纹」
「风流潇洒的大表哥」
「inga  suki!  单推了!」
「手书可以抹...」
「兜兜有nyanya」
「没睡觉好困」
「你可以在我中的手书上留个唇印」
「(棠霜)ベゴニア」
「FiendGray」
「在下银桑」
「哲星」