forty
yes
i'm thinking of buying
that's nice
of lego legends
but i'm so that it is
so that at the
monster hunter
i have the game
but i haven't touched it yet
i will
i will get it some day
oh
i play a lot of freedom games
but i guess that doesn't really matter
i can't really show you guys that
never
ever
i met attire
number
although atlanta
i cannot
little boo
don't know
a chicken night
you know
at the mock up
can you walk now to give me
at the time
or
what's
never over
monkey
lucky sky
i quoted 18
among us
sure
corner otoko wa
kettle
no
i want to talk
my
okay
oh
and i have to share my goals for the year
i really wanna
have
many
different
kind
eight
i was thinking of good night session
and then i can sing all of the kind of
slow songs
so
make you guys
go to sleep next week
and then it
yes
okay
ya
and then
uh collab
with my success
oh
i was hoping to
learn
learn to play the guitar and sing
and then
of it so much to ask
but maybe
maybe
just
but you
oh
and we see this text
and the authorities say
how come
i wonder if that's the way this many people on the application itself
chen guo
kapoor
ccb ball
oh
i know
i know this
you mean you mean discover a fair
yes
are you going to cover
this scheme
i know that one
you did fuck
oh
sarah
right
i like to sing that one
what do you call it
you raise me up
the the could it more sughero please
come
please go
i'll try to figure out if i can do this
sometime soon
oh have you guys watched romero in juliet
there's a lot of
do they have a new version of the song
and it's really nice
i like that question
songs of west side
nothing comes to my mind right now
but i'm sure no one of one or two songs
what else
i can sing a few english songs
coplay
maybe
i used to
sorry
home are in cto boko
married to move out
twitter
say
i think this is all of my goals
i have an
my mind
if i have more
i can always tell you guys
wei
great what you come up
because your what
that's
i used
oh my god
i used two hours
to do s l introduction
oh
my god
i am so sorry
two hours for a self introduction
i come to believe myself
thank you
so
oh my god
what am i saying
thank you guys
for the
presence
i will read them later
one by one
thank you guys so much
scarborough fair like to sing
that's something
should we
should we make this
i think
this mean that i can end now
i'm done
and then with my thoughts
only eight o'clock
i have a last one prepared
actually
i really appreciate you guys coming here today to watch me
i feel like i had a lot of mess ups
and
you know
the network
we're then going well
i am too nervous
i don't know how to use
this application
but we're good
very good
forget there
today is your english listening class
free english lessons
feel welcome
nine
live
let us place the order together
something i really want to place over
although although i haven't found all nine hundred yamaha
we're
oh my god please don't please don't cut this fortune out
i don't want to see myself
if you months later
let us
but i was going to the last
when i have prepared today
i heard you guys like it because i watched a movie and it was really nice
wanna you wanna
want to get is what i'm going to say
it's the the movie was about as if our cats
qingwan
but no
no
i don't want it
i don't want to say anything
no
but there
we talked about this just because i was like
you talk
nine is for come
for come
for
cats and mouse
no
it's it's is a japanese song
oppo
or instagram to kansas
a study that we have
a ringer soldier
career changing
how to
it got equal