let's just
costs has taken
i didn't have to
i think i got to keep tong qi
i must say
thank you
my province is the next time
the next time i won't be so nervous
qiqi
pop
create fan group and captain
who face
mm
i will think about it
thank you
the next stream
maybe
maybe tomorrow
ah
encoder
ankle
uncle or not
and then i got stainless scissor more
that he's a good and evil
ahh
we
you need any guy in this
but now
but
that's the joyful cheer often you release from overtime
do you do to be a
riviera
nubia
if you a dog
hotel in seattle uh we can make a comment or mail
rubiah
revenge
time to say goodbye
i can sing it in italian
clone
i heard a rubia rupiah
oh look to say
no
yoda
i
i tried imitating me some money
what what we are don't settle
bochuan li xuan
oppo
what was that again
it
let it go
this have a disney time
sometime
lee
dubia
do a talk to you
do you have ski
believer
is it a english
what i worked
dubia are touting me out
but i'm sorry
that wasn't rubia
put i
that's like
oops
us to soft again
zehui
thank you guys for watching
thank you
she said
reflecting
so what hong kong's hu jintao
ganzi home 10kg
so sorry
i so sorry
but thank you guys so much for coming to watch
i really appreciate it from the photo of my heart
thank you
thank you so much
you complete it up
i like equal
non good man
in the
washington one carlo
now
one
the whole batch
but i do zola
holiday code
but anna
will pay a lot
we hear the end
thank you guys so much
just
thank you
oh
chia mei
said to me
mini
go
thank you
okay
i'm gonna i'm going to go read the
people
who joined the membership
thank you so much
the director
she is the culture
sso hotel
mas
la
kangkong
three
i opened the thing to comment
since pang qiong
how do you
oh god
thank you
thank you so much
wait
i need to read
thank you guys so much for coming today
b
as a tax on
thank you so much for the membership
three
seven
ten
thank you for the membership
asian
one
none
thank you
yao hui 2
thank you for the membership
wang s
a
d
tao
jing
yihao
thank you for the membership
in a country aqua
thank you
time
timer
time reborn
oh god
thank you for the membership
now we are
yuan xing zizhou
a o e
thank you
patrice 5fun
ashtray
zz
thank you
addis
cardio core
summing
winning
trimming
oh no
thank you
uniqlo adiga
snow is it
thank you
oh my god
what is his name
q
everybody
that will pew
p
thank you
ojha
wu shehe liu xuantong official
thank you
do you know a coco
toy chihuahua radiator
you met the total kerrigan yin haslir
qiu
topaz
thank you so much
more
more for what
i'm so sorry
thank you
kongming
comment
thank you
shen yu xing
yan
thank you
okay
and you got
we
your own
xiao
the thought to equal part moon
thank you
see
you
thank you
two
oh
two thousand
and i got to guatemala to senoko
thank you
tian lang xiao
yu sheng
thank you
dg
v
thank you
ya
hua
thank you
hard to
two
do
thank you
hello to thank you sincerely
jiang nan
nan
official alligator link to the
then rice
then you
oh
uh
baoqing santika
fifth
to
that's so bad
thank you
qi qi zhe
chen xiao
thank you
was she
wu
did xiao li
thank you
did i miss anyone
uh
tmall add got to see
thank you so much
guys
i took
enjoy it
and he got
so i go when they retire
mccool
dai yutang
to thank you
but uh
how do you go
are regarded zodiac
sixteen
she
thank you guys so much
no onion
dug device
hi
i'm thomas
yeah
i got
sixteen
she got
thank you so much
there was way too many super chats and i could have written fast enough
but thank you for bearing with me
and the presence
thank you
thank you so much
what tomato
i hope
i hope i can bring more
nice content
see you guys
well
i would just appreciate
if you can
if you guys can listen to me sing
i'll be really happy
sorry
did i pronounce your
the name wrong
what am i supposed to pronounce
it is
oh
dot thieves
oh my god
i was so sorry
i'm here for two and a half hours
i'm so sorry
i will improve my chinese
i swear
maybe next time i will read your names
ah
i see
thank you guys
so much
good night
please
take care
okay
some of this hype
but i
sweet dreams
good night
okayu to are you
thank you
what's gonna express how thankful i am
i see you guys
again
spice