thank you
i would appreciate if you send my name on top
banzai
and tong
she stated
continuing your
statue
li beijia
you
uh
two
mattia
well
oh no
we may find
t t p
huh
what
what was she
hdmi xiaoning
the trauma
f b i opened the door
no
photo
oh no
but if if it's if it's
if it's here for me
then everyone here is going to the hospital with me
that's the only way
i wish you guys
obviously
as well
reclaims each other together
will be washing through the night
but we washing through the night
oh
by the way
i heard i heard a lot of people complaining about how loud the music was
i'm so sorry
i
i am so bad at using
so bad he took videos
didn't make a memorable impact in your ears
congo v zero mah
say
sister
i know
i know that song
i
i can
i can go learn it
i am
yantai punched me
please
panqu
yao
hi
cma
you want to punch
you wanna punch
my friend
i will give you
what you want
hey
do you want a pants
okay
takasaki
pretty the dial
i'm a nice girl
i don't try ten people
that was in me
that wasn't me
took out tai chi zheng zheng de in guoqian
so
die
who would i want to collect with in the future
hello
mazur
i want to collab with
i want a collab with my sisters
first
lada
atv
and then the next one i wanna collab with
maybe
other
three language
be your service
or
yesterday
mamma 2019
oh
hammer
yes
please
do
toyo koto
you want to hear me scold you
he said
is that what you want
call that with hand over idea
yes
please
can i speak
m i t e m i t e partisan
uh-huh
you can't
you can't contact me
i see you
and that being tricked
hm
right
i forgot about what i was talking about
i was saying that i was very bad at video editing
and you guys years were all bleeding
so i was thinking
singing the second part of
the song
oh wait
not the second part
part of
the older sisters
to make up for it
because
that wasn't what i meant to
do i didn't mean to make you play from your years
that dagger collab with hammer armario
a
oh no
i i have
i have a dagger and he have a hammer
we are going to rock the world
lego rock world
psycho psycho
and i
seiko does it
psycho
you may
who is
we can
we can go
thank you
we
pattison pattison
guangben
comedy
i
of the we are army
we are early
we are in army
wait
you make me forget what i was talking about
again
we go back
we go back to our car
xugang baker
is a gpa flat steel plate
is that what it means
common steel
can he
no
i'm supposed to apologize for making your ears
i'm going back
let me apologize
wait
where is it
manna
tomato dosa
shan hao de
ben gunn
ben
what
what does that mean
what is what is that
why is everybody is shield
i'm so confused