no
i'm supposed to apologize
i'm going to apologize right now
i'm going to sing another song
i'm
because i prepared this early this morning today
so i'm not very familiar with it
but
please
listen
book
oh
i missed it
everything to me
trembling
from the
something is familiar
like a dream
i can reach the quality
i can send you the
like friend
i always
right
and it feels like guy
the fortress
could security
do you have secrets
but you don't have to
sure
and dying to meet
share his
it's your turn
oh
you do
well
i've been looking for my
so
i'm ready to
oh my life i have been too
but i'm here for he said
good reason
so
understand
this today
i find
going to her
go
do you have
let me see
to me
thank you
make me you
there's a
you want your
was that
set a good enough apology
thank you
or longer due chen shui guo wei
the pizza
haiquan
she is from the piazza of
is this the last question
liucheng
how big
how big is still
thank you on sound party
i
i really love this
me
six inch
oh no
six in hotel big city
inch
how many centimeters is six inch
but six and eleven
isn't that almost twice
not changing the mozilla
you
tama
i know you
oh my god
i'm so behind myself
sorry
no
i know
oh no
this is not supposed to be the case
i am supposed to continue
right
hi
he
well
you can find out more by jie shao
and the editor
putting that in
could you think i did it on zi ah
but he stood arrested on
is it would ever
i would
i have a dog
i did a bit
japan 1
spooky
to go
so what day
saidu
my birth
stay
bye
japan
ya
thank yoga
the thunder bay
over the decades
bye
and then
and then i'll tell you my favorite things
i like the color gray
oh my god
is this how you write
wait
does it have
does it have a
never mind
and then
oh
we have to decide to art
tech and the fantech
wait
let me
bye bye
i buy this
which would be
art
i take
oh
we have the same birthday
data is the new way
what are some things
i like to wash
i like to watch
check
check out cosima
check out your kashima
okay
the matter
thank you for your visit
takeshi yifu
but what you
what should i technique
guo
oh
my god
it's so ugly
sanqingshan
then try
shuzhen
dante
uh
what
what person on me
maple antique
well while going mei xiang yu jie
comment
the more the more i got to
lao ban duan qi
what
pen
shisha
uh
were wasi masonic peasant pants
susan soda
kheema
can you marry me
are you
are you a beautiful little lady
but i can't marry more than one person
it's illegal
ya
the answer
i said
one
guogang
i'm new to the job
i haven't watched anyone's clothes yet
but if i do
if i do
i'll keep it to myself
i'm not telling you
guys
let's see
i'm keeping it
realize so um
one day
one day i'll get to wash everyone's clothes
was soon menglian dado
li yao
toddler j
j
yi hui jia qiao qiao xi
i don't know
but it
but he said
it said that i don't
secret
not supposed to say it
i have a stash
and my three hole
they're not supposed to stay