it
yes
i am
oh
you are a official
wonton
but
mm
it's it's one of my hobbies
minus thompson
everyone's everyone's
only one
be sure
you haven't think of it
but what should be a tab
no
mama
simota mama
in
so
automatic is
hey
this is nice
oh
in in
in art
it sounds kind of cool
pingguoyuan
hi xiao
what jixiangju jiahuan
what
well
gonna go
take that
quit quit sima
the question
hi
okay
i must
in gulu
in koi
i'm green
socma
let's change a museum
that was
that was there for way too long
pm
why does this sound so
right
dollar is green
what about what about the fed tightening
but i
but i was just free from vegan
to
but i'm not going to me
and you guys are going to
in
we can vote for this
oh
should decide it now
oh my god
how do you write
to
oops
no
data
twitter
kuwait
so much
bar
weave the better
true true
right whips
yes
yes you guys
you guys will be gone
and then i'll eat you
this one
should we go with ingots and 12in one of the yoga
could you call it
according
yingguo
kuai zhu tang
am i the one cooking or either one being cooked
i can
love korean matador gunner
paton autodesk made to
fan page
contaminated
okay
queen is successful
ok
thank you
you
i'm the one that cooked
i'm good at cooking
i cook
you guys
i am not the for
haiti
it
i can't eat me
oh
and but on my hobbies
i
timing
she got a gun
xiaomi gen
yue weimin
your way in
deming
oh yeah
because
i think i got
i bought my
window system
so
i am so excited
can we play together some time
we can all play together
oh
i play so many cells
again
violet town majeski
and i also really like
what's the last one
you feel like
but like your one
smash brothers
mm
what else
i usually like to sing a lot of me
oh yeah
i was thinking of trying apex
i haven't
started
twenty eight yet
but i hope we get so
it's something
mario
mario up
i have
put him at tusky
on a dusty
what else do i think i like
i like to sing a lot of
and my favorite female singer is still set
two
nihongo octagon
lee
that data
dan
no
we have a lot of tailors
refuse
she is so cool
hope it out
as the most
well
it's a classic
but i love phantom
love
sorry
she had to release a new song
a cover of the new song
and so
good
shenhua weg
someone sorry
you play well and keep raising
that's
i'm so bad
at
her actually lost more than 15
and i want on
once
ki
hot game
how are you
what are yo
how do i give a negative a war
if i
if i play a horror game
and then i won't be able to shower for two weeks
no horror
what are the medal
what else dialect
residence inn
people escape from raccoon city
really
what are some kind of
what are some games you guys have to recommend
i should write them down
and then i can play down someday
resident evil
and
luca
the jelly wo wo wo wo 1
can can superstar
would that person
your
xiao jie jie
jie
well
i forgot
what's the other one
what was the other game
oh
for buffet
learn how to pay
mahjong
oh
devil may cry
okay
i'll go check them out
taizhou
bohui
i learn
corroded
finger
how do you read that one
what is this
yes
i can play
you know
m h west and h
i can pay
you know
i am pretty
oh
and i like playing monopoly
a monopoly takes ages
so many games
oh
i see it
ahh
it's a bad word
bye bye
minecraft
yes
i've played minecraft a lot
if there's a chance
maybe
oh my god
so
forty
yes
i'm thinking of buying
that's nice
of lego legends
but i'm so that it is
so that at the
monster hunter
i have the game
but i haven't touched it yet
i will
i will get it some day
oh
i play a lot of freedom games
but i guess that doesn't really matter
i can't really show you guys that
never
ever
i met attire
number
although atlanta
i cannot
little boo
don't know
a chicken night
you know
at the mock up
can you walk now to give me
at the time
or
what's
never over
monkey
lucky sky
i quoted 18
among us
sure
corner otoko wa
kettle
no
i want to talk
my
okay
oh
and i have to share my goals for the year
i really wanna
have
many
different
kind
eight
i was thinking of good night session
and then i can sing all of the kind of
slow songs
so
make you guys
go to sleep next week
and then it
yes
okay
ya
and then
uh collab
with my success
oh
i was hoping to
learn
learn to play the guitar and sing
and then
of it so much to ask
but maybe
maybe
just
but you
oh
and we see this text
and the authorities say
how come
i wonder if that's the way this many people on the application itself
chen guo
kapoor
ccb ball
oh
i know
i know this
you mean you mean discover a fair
yes
are you going to cover
this scheme
i know that one
you did fuck
oh
sarah
right
i like to sing that one
what do you call it
you raise me up
the the could it more sughero please
come
please go
i'll try to figure out if i can do this
sometime soon
oh have you guys watched romero in juliet
there's a lot of
do they have a new version of the song
and it's really nice
i like that question
songs of west side
nothing comes to my mind right now
but i'm sure no one of one or two songs
what else
i can sing a few english songs
coplay
maybe
i used to
sorry
home are in cto boko
married to move out
twitter
say
i think this is all of my goals
i have an
my mind
if i have more
i can always tell you guys
wei
great what you come up
because your what
that's
i used
oh my god
i used two hours
to do s l introduction
oh
my god
i am so sorry
two hours for a self introduction
i come to believe myself
thank you
so
oh my god
what am i saying
thank you guys
for the
presence
i will read them later
one by one
thank you guys so much
scarborough fair like to sing
that's something
should we
should we make this
i think
this mean that i can end now
i'm done
and then with my thoughts
only eight o'clock
i have a last one prepared
actually
i really appreciate you guys coming here today to watch me
i feel like i had a lot of mess ups
and
you know
the network
we're then going well
i am too nervous
i don't know how to use
this application
but we're good
very good
forget there
today is your english listening class
free english lessons
feel welcome
nine
live
let us place the order together
something i really want to place over
although although i haven't found all nine hundred yamaha
we're
oh my god please don't please don't cut this fortune out
i don't want to see myself
if you months later
let us
but i was going to the last
when i have prepared today
i heard you guys like it because i watched a movie and it was really nice
wanna you wanna
want to get is what i'm going to say
it's the the movie was about as if our cats
qingwan